[
    {   
        "number":1,
        "question":"Which is not permitive Datatype ?",
        "answer 1":"Char",
        "answer 2":"arr",
        "answer 3":"float",
        "answer 4":"int",
        "rightAnswer":"arr"
    },
    {   
        "number":2,
        "question":"C++ is a superset of :",
        "answer 1":"C",
        "answer 2":"C#",
        "answer 3":"JavaScript",
        "answer 4":"python",
        "rightAnswer":"C"
    },
    {   
        "number":3,
        "question":"What is run time polymorphism ?",
        "answer 1":"It provides fast execution because it is known at the compile time.",
        "answer 2":"It is achieved by function overloading and operator overloading.",
        "answer 3":"It can be achieved by virtual functions and pointers.",
        "answer 4":"none of the above",
        "rightAnswer":"It can be achieved by virtual functions and pointers."
    },
    {   
        "number":4,
        "question":"C++ differs compared to C in which of these ?",
        "answer 1":"C++ is an object-oriented programming language.",
        "answer 2":"C++ is a procedure-oriented programming language.",
        "answer 3":"C++ does not support data hiding.",
        "answer 4":"Function and operator overloading are not supported in C++",
        "rightAnswer":"C++ is an object-oriented programming language."
    },
    {
        "number":5,
        "question":"All of choices are the C++ access specifiers except ?",
        "answer 1":"public",
        "answer 2":"private",
        "answer 3":"protected",
        "answer 4":"semi-public",
        "rightAnswer":"semi-public"
    },
    {
        "number":6,
        "question":"what is Shallow Copy ?",
        "answer 1":"Shallow copy stores the references of objects to the original memory address.",
        "answer 2":"Shallow copy makes a new and separate copy of an entire object with its unique memory address.",
        "answer 3":"Shallow copy is comparatively slower.",
        "answer 4":"Shallow copy does not reflect changes made to the new/copied object in the original object",
        "rightAnswer":"Shallow copy stores the references of objects to the original memory address."
    },
    {
        "number":7,
        "question":"Memory used by an array is ?",
        "answer 1":"Contiguous",
        "answer 2":"Non-contiguous",
        "answer 3":"Not determined",
        "answer 4":"None of the above",
        "rightAnswer":"Contiguous"
    },
    {
        "number":8,
        "question":"What is the size of void in C++? ?",
        "answer 1":"0",
        "answer 2":"2",
        "answer 3":"8",
        "answer 4":"4",
        "rightAnswer":"0"
    },
    {
        "number":9,
        "question":"What is an abstract class?",
        "answer 1":"Class declared with abstract keyword",
        "answer 2":"Class which has at least one pure virtual function",
        "answer 3":"Class which has exactly one virtual function",
        "answer 4":"None of the above",
        "rightAnswer":"Class which has at least one pure virtual function"
    },
    {
        "number":10,
        "question":"Which operator can not be overloaded in C++?",
        "answer 1":"+",
        "answer 2":"::",
        "answer 3":"*",
        "answer 4":"++",
        "rightAnswer":"::"
    }
]